University of Connecticut 1987.0011
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VII: Speeches, undated, 1977-1985
  - "To members of the University community re racial slurs", 1979 September 26 (Box 38:, Folder 1620)
  - "Speech to CDC Association, Benton Museum", 1979 October 2 (Box 38:, Folder 1621)
  - "Red Cross College seminar in Farmington", 1979 October 3 (Box 38:, Folder 1622)
  - "Metaonia speech", 1979 October 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1623)
  - "Statement re Day of Metaonia", 1979 October 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1624)
  - "Address to Sons of Italy, Hartford Hilton", 1979 October 7 (Box 38:, Folder 1625)
  - "Address to UNICO, Waterbury", 1979 October 8 (Box 38:, Folder 1626)
  - "Statement re basketball team", 1979 October 9 (Box 38:, Folder 1627)
  - "Greetings from Gordon W. Tasker, dedication of W.B. Young building", 1979 October 13 (Box 38:, Folder 1628)
  - "Remarks at dedication of W.B. Young building", 1979 October 13 (Box 38:, Folder 1629)
  - "Statement to the Joint Committee on Education", 1979 October 16 (Box 38:, Folder 1630)
  - "Address to Roper Center", 1979 October 26 (Box 38:, Folder 1631)
  - "Agustus Carroll memorial lecture, American Association of Medical Colleges meeting", 1979 November 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1632)
  - "Address to Honor Society of Phi Kappa Phi", 1979 November 12 (Box 38:, Folder 1633)
  - "Address at Focus 80, Case Western Reserve University", 1979 November 15 (Box 38:, Folder 1634)
  - "Remarks to Connecticut Farm Bureau Association, Inc.", 1979 November 29 (Box 38:, Folder 1635)
  - "Energy statement on Board of Trustees", 1979 December 14 (Box 38:, Folder 1636)
  - "Statement on the University of Bridgeport", 1979 December 14 (Box 38:, Folder 1637)
  - "Address to paramedic graduates, UConn Health Center", 1979 December 20 (Box 38:, Folder 1638)
  - "Dental Education: A Mirror into the Future of Dental Practice", 1978 September 30 (Box 38:, Folder 1639)
  - "Address to the alumni banquet of the School of Allied Health Professions", 1978 June 9 (Box 38:, Folder 1640)
  - "Drs. Irving Eichenbaum and Naomi Dunn: The Essence of Professionalism", 1977 April 4 (Box 38:, Folder 1641)
  - Speeches, undated (Box 38:, Folder 1642)
  - Speeches: pre-UConn, undated (Box 38:, Folder 1643)